Narrator: Inspector Granger arrived at about 9.00.
He was a short man with white hair and pale blue eyes.
Amanda, Barbara, Claudia, and Gordon were in the living room.
The inspector came in.
Inspector: ÔMr Travers died between midnight last night and 7.00 this morning,Ő he said.
ÔSomebody in this room killed him.Ő
Narrator: He looked at them one by one, but nobody spoke.
Inspector: ÔMrs Travers, I want to talk to you first.
Come into the study with me, please.Ő
Narrator: Amanda followed the inspector into the study and they sat down.
Inspector: ÔWhat did your husband do after dinner last night?Ő
Amanda: ÔWe finished dinner at about 9.30.
Then Jeremy said he was tired and he went to bed.Ő
Inspector: ÔDid you go to bed then?Ő
Amanda: ÔNo, I didnŐt. I went for a walk in the garden.Ő
Inspector: ÔWhat time did you go to bed?Ő
Amanda: ÔAbout quarter to twelve.Ő
Inspector: ÔWas your husband asleep?Ő
Amanda: ÔI donŐt know, Inspector.
WeÉwe slept in different rooms.
But I saw that his door was closed.Ő
Inspector: ÔDid you hear anything when you were in your room?Ő
Amanda: ÔYes, I heard JeremyŐs bedroom door.
It opened.
I thought it was Jeremy. Then it closed again.
I read in bed for half an hour and then I went to sleep.Ő
Inspector: ÔWhat time did you get up this morning?Ő
Amanda: ÔI got up at about 7.15. I had breakfast and at 8.00 I took a cup of tea to my husband.
I found him in bed. He wasÉdead.Ő
Inspector: ÔTell me, Mrs Travers, did you love your husband?Ő
Amanda: ÔJeremy isÉwas a difficult man.Ő
Inspector: ÔBut did you love him, Mrs Travers?Ő
Amanda: Ô ÔNo, Inspector. I hated him.Ő